

# DANNY KRUISWIJK

## DETAILS •

06-37275714 dannykruiswijk@hotmail.com

· LINKS ·

dannykruiswijk.com

SKILLS

C++

C#

Python

Unreal Engine

Unity Engine

Perforce

HOBBIES

Gaming, Yoga, Board games, Biking, Frisbeeing

LANGUAGES

Dutch

English

#### PROFILE

My passion for games started when I was playing games as a kid. Over time, my passion evolved from playing games to developing games.

At first I found joy in working on small indie projects with commercial engines but as I got more experienced I got intrigued by custom solutions and AAA-scale games.

Today I work with Unreal and custom solutions as a Tools Programmer with C++ / C# where I focus on usability, efficiency and performance while improving my fellow developers workflow while making games.

I have made amazing memories playing games in my life and I hope as a developer to give other people that same experience.

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Gamedeveloper Intern at Alterego Games

February 2017 — July 2017

Programming games in Unity with C#

Programmer, Level Designer at Alterego Games

July 2017 - September 2017

Virtual Reality Developer Intern at Scopic VR

September 2017 — February 2018

Creating experiences and simulations for the Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Gear VR and Google Daydream using Unity C#  $\,$ 

#### EDUCATION

Game Development, Mediacollege Amsterdam

September 2014 — July 2018

Graduated

Creating games with Unity C#

Creative Media & Game Technologies (IGAD), NHTV Breda University of Applied Sciences September 2019 — July 2023

Working on custom engines in C++, with a focus on Tools programming Multi disciplinary development, creating experiences with the Unreal Engine